[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Helena] I have a job for you.
Protect the diamonds
I've sent for the charity event.
Make sure that it gets there.
[Raul] Get ready because
we have another mission.
A certain package will arrive.
Diamonds worth 20 million.
We'll take them all.
[Lily] But we have to go there
so I can find out
who Helena Montoya really is.
That's when I'll find out
whether she's my enemy
or my ally.
You're here to seduce
my husband again, aren't you?
That's so last month. I've moved on.
Who could my new flavor of the month be?
[Emilia] Please escort this
little birdbrain out of here.
-[Natalie] I can walk!
-[Emilia] And do her a good job.
[Damian] Only an idiot
would betray Red Dragon.
[man] Someone's following us.
[gunshots]
-[explosion]
-[Damian laughing]
You better practice first,
if you want to get a punch in!
[Natalie] I already saved you before.
And thank you for saving me.
Now we're even.
[Jepoy] Just be careful.
I don't want this happening again.
[Helena] I would like to introduce to you
my long-lost daughter,
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
[Lily] Now I know why she
wants to get close to me.
[Helena] I only have good
intentions for this town.
Why don't you join me and
my latest project for the town?
Sure, Helena. Sure.
[Julio] Those diamonds are only
beautiful to a fool
who thinks they don't come with a price.
[Camia] Be wary. You don't know
who you're up against.
They may have buried Ivy Aguas,
but her words still remain.
So, to Emilia and Helena…
Don't try me.
[tense music playing]
We don't have an appointment, Helena.
I came here to surprise you.
You won't kick me out, will you?
I brought you something.
If it isn't the famous Lily Cruz.
[Lily chuckles softly]
Why, of course
I'm going to welcome
a very sweet lady like you.
Oh… Helena, I have to say,
your causes have been so remarkable.
That's why I decided to pay you a visit.
'Cause now I am your number one fan.
I'm curious as to how
a high-profile jewelry designer,
artist, socially responsible humanitarian,
became Emilia Ardiente's biological mother
and Julio Ardiente's ex-lover.
No offense, Helena, but being involved
with that family
is so outside your profile.
It's really a long story, Lily.
I don't think you have the EQ
to listen to my life story.
No offense.
[tense music playing]
Helena, try me. Try me.
I'll listen. Promise.
[birds chirping]
Helena?
No. I don't know anyone named Helena.
Last night, during the event
at the capitol,
Helena Montoya introduced
herself as Emilia's mother.
That makes her your grandmother.
Aren't you interested
in getting to know her?
Have you ever thought
of returning to your family?
Don't you think about them anymore?
I know why you're asking me this.
You're making sure I've really changed.
Do you still not trust me until now?
Thing is, Arnaldo,
you can't dictate what
people think about you.
What's important
is you do good for others,
and one day, your actions
will prove who you really are.
[uplifting music playing]
[Camia] We need to tighten
the security at night.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Understood?
-All right. You may go.
[Damian] Camia.
Did Lily push through
with her meeting with Helena?
Yes, Damian.
But we both know that Lily won't
go to war unprepared.
[unsettling music playing]
Damian?
Is there a problem?
Do you know anything about
Helena Montoya that we don't?
[tense music playing]
Damian!
About Red Dragon, yes.
Red Dragon brought down Lily's business.
How is she connected to Helena Montoya?
Lily Cruz is Ivy Aguas.
I know she'll get past all of this.
If she managed to fool
the Ardientes back then,
then you're right,
we have nothing to worry about.
I promised myself that after I gave birth,
my baby and I would escape
and live in peace.
-[doctor] There's been a problem.
-[Helena] But it didn't happen.
-[doctor] But I promise…
-Where's my baby?!
…we will do everything to save your baby.
Where are you taking my baby?!
[Helena] Julio made me believe
my baby was dead.
And for so many years…
[Helena crying]
For so many years,
I thought Emilia was dead.
But when I found out she was
alive, I searched for her.
And now, we're finally reunited.
[sobs] I'm sorry. I just…
I get really passionate when
I talk about the people I love.
[exhales] How about you, Lily?
I heard you and your mother
were separated too.
All because of the Ardientes.
That's not all, Helena.
The Ardientes killed my father.
And they made my family's life hell.
And you staged an elaborate revenge plot.
Because it's only an eye for an eye.
[tense music playing]
It's not my place to say this, but…
I hope that you will forgive my family.
But if you loathe them, why are you here?
Am I now your enemy too?
Or is it because…
you're planning to use me?
Is that also why you haven't
declared war against me, Helena?
I'm not an Ardiente.
[chuckles] Tell you what, Lily--
I enjoy talking to you. Why don't we…
see each other again?
Lunch or dinner, perhaps?
I thought you'd never ask, Helena.
[suspenseful music playing]
So…
You finally convinced
your mother to fight Lily Cruz.
Why is that?
Don't you find me a formidable
ally anymore,
that you had to run to your
mother to find a new supporter?
[sighs]
Papa, what are you upset about?
That I didn't approach you?
Or that I have a new ally in Mama?
Don't be too presumptuous, my dear.
Don't expect that your mother
can beat Lily Cruz.
Lily Cruz and your Mama
have a lot in common, you know.
Maybe, in the end,
they might get along,
and you'll end up in the dust.
[both chuckle]
Well you can't poison
my mind anymore, Papa.
In fact, I'm organizing
a reunion with my son and Mama.
And you're not invited.
Who's left in the dust now, huh?
[chuckles mockingly]
Well…
Good luck…
to your mini-reunion,
good riddance,
and enjoy in the depths of Hades.
Clan of devils.
-I lost my appetite.
-Good for you.
She asked for your forgiveness?
Helena Montoya?
Talk is cheap, Diego.
I don't get swayed by words.
And her daughter is Emilia.
We really shouldn't trust her.
But she let it all slide.
She might not be an Ardiente,
but I'll find out every last
detail about Helena Montoya.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Arnaldo] Diego are you still
having trouble
with Helena Montoya?
Because Anna told me
that she's my grandmother.
Is that right?
We're concerned about anything
related to the Ardientes.
Ah, okay.
Then she's a bad person too.
I was just thinking…
do you still think I'm a bad person?
[pensive music playing]
[foreboding music playing]
What the hell are you doing here?!
Hey, Diego.
You think I don't know
that you want to take advantage
of Arnaldo's sickness
for your own personal agenda?
-I'm not like you!
-Yeah, right! I know.
I know what you want to do, Diego.
You want to take Arnaldo down
because he's sick right now.
But, I'll tell you,
he's going to rise again, okay?
Arnaldo, get away from him.
Okay, you. Toss out the garbage!
Hold on a second! What are you doing?
Ouch!
Stop it! I said, get Diego!
Why did you hurt Arnaldo?
-He was in the way, ma'am.
-I was in the way?
Enough, okay? This is enough.
You're going with me.
[Arnaldo] I'm not going with you!
The only thing that Diego did
was be a good brother to me.
You're coming with me
to meet your grandmother.
You… This isn't over.
Let's go!
Open the door! Hurry!
[car doors closing]
[car engine turns over]
That Diego Torillo has
always been a nuisance
to the Ardiente family, Mama.
Why haven't you had him killed yet?
If you had, you wouldn't
be having this problem.
You know, Mama, you're right.
But it's never too late.
I want Diego Torillo's head.
Oh, I have the perfect man for that.
The formidable Jaguar.
Jaguar? You know him, Mama?
[Emilia scoffs]
What a small world,
and lots of coincidence, Mama.
I know him too.
-Really?
-Yes, Mama.
I know him very well.
[dramatic music playing]
-Here.
-Oh. Thanks.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. This is nothing.
[exhales]
Are you sure about what you did earlier?
Did I do something wrong?
I just did what I thought was right.
You don't plan on meeting
your grandmother?
Come to think of it, I do.
I want to meet her, but it's a mess there.
Yes, they're rich, but they're miserable.
I'd rather stay here.
It's really quiet here, but I'm happy.
That's why I was hoping you'd tell them
that I just want to stay here.
[uplifting music playing]
[exhales]
Oh! Jaguar, darling!
This is your next bull's-eye.
Diego Torillo.
Special request of my daughter.
Isn't she lovely?
Um…
So, Jaguar, when do we discuss
Diego Torillo's murder?
Just call me when you want the job done.
[laughs] Mama! Whee! I'm so happy!
[sighs] Let's drink to that.
[glasses clink]
I can't do this. I won't do this!
[action music playing]
[Helena] This is your next bull's-eye.
Diego Torillo.
Special request of my daughter.
Pay attention.
That's what I want to do
to my new enemies.
Because fire melts gold.
I want to burn Lily Cruz alive!
[tense music playing]
-[grunts]
-[phone clatters]
[tense music playing]
Damian.
What's going on?
Why do you have this? Answer me, Damian!
Where is Lily?
But if you loathe them, why are you here?
Am I now your enemy too?
Or is it because
you're planning to use me?
Is that also why you haven't
declared war against me, Helena?
I'm not an Ardiente. Tell you what, Lily--
I enjoy talking to you. Why don't we…
see each other again?
Lunch or dinner, perhaps?
I've already played this game
before, Helena.
So, hold on to your head.
Because I'm going to uncover
every secret you've got.
I will charm you…
and trap you like a moth to a flame.
I will be the sweetest, most glamorous,
fabulous mother you never had, Lily Cruz.
And once you've grown so attached to me…
that's when I'll swallow
you whole! [hisses]
[laughs]
[foreboding music playing]
[phone rings]
Mercedes.
Madam, I can't contact Jaguar.
You can't contact Jaguar?
Idiot! You act like
you're not my underling!
You know what to do.
So, stop wasting my time.
[foreboding music continues]
Don't worry, Mom.
I'll let you know once
I've met up with Helena.
-As always, be careful.
-I will.
I'll be leaving now.
Lily.
Yes, Uncle?
Lily, you're facing
a very unpredictable enemy.
So, listen to me. Red Dragon is…
[suspenseful music swelling]
[tense music]
[eerie music]
Hurry. You should leave.
Be careful out there.
Take care.
[tense music playing]
[car door closes]
Camia, go on inside.
[tense music playing]
[car engine turns over]
[tense music continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
[exhales deeply]
What are you doing here?
I'm glad you got the message quickly.
But the next time you decide to
cut off communication with us,
you better make sure I don't find you.
[suspenseful music]
[Mercedes] This is for you.
And this is the gun
I'll be using on Camia and Lily
the moment you defy Red Dragon's orders.
[tense music playing]
[Lily and Helena chuckling]
This is the best dim sum in the metro.
So, I guess you really
enjoy Chinese cuisine?
From time to time.
But, you know what, Lily?
I'm very happy that you're here today.
-My day's been made.
-[Lily chuckles]
But more so, if you accepted my proposal.
I'm organizing…
a women empowerment seminar.
And I want us to work together.
I want you to be the guest speaker.
What do you say?
Sure, Helena.
After all, I'm the type of woman
who never backs down
from a fight or lets anyone get in my way.
I am Lily Cruz.
And, like I told the Ardientes,
I am indestructible.
[both laugh]
Well, that makes the two of us.
We have so much in common.
We could be best friends!
To friendship.
[glasses clink]
[tense music playing]
-Where are you going, Damian?
-Don't mind me, Camia.
Damian, wait!
Where are you going? Manila? Work?
I know there's something
you're not telling me!
I won't let you leave
until you tell me the truth!
I don't have to tell you anything.
What is it you were about to
tell Lily about Red Dragon?
Do you know anything about Red Dragon?
Answer me, Damian!
Are you part of Red Dragon's syndicate?
[line ringing]
Hello, Jaguar.
I thought you were avoiding me.
You were so cold earlier.
[scoffs]
What are you talking about, Emilia?
Because when Red Dragon and I
asked you to kill Diego Torillo,
you just said a few words and left.
Oh, about what happened…
Sorry about that. I was just tired.
So, when do you want me to do it?
Anyway, do it at your own
pace and leisure.
But I'd just like to remind you,
I don't like waiting too long.
You can count on me, Emilia.
I'll give you Diego Torillo's head
on a silver platter.
You are so awesome!
No.
But I know of Red Dragon.
Her name was everywhere
when I was still a criminal.
Because those who stood in
her way were killed mercilessly.
That's why I asked Lily
to stop messing with her
before it's too late.
I can't let anything bad happen to her…
and especially not to you, Camia.
[dramatic music playing]
[phone ringing]
-Go on.
-[ringing continues]
-Dad?
-[Raul] Hello, Diego.
Listen closely, son.
You need to hide.
Because you're Red Dragon's next target.
What? How did you find out?
Who's Red Dragon? Do you know her?
[Raul] I'll explain everything
in due time.
But for now, you have to watch your back.
Thanks, Dad. But I'm not afraid of her.
And we'll do everything
to bring Red Dragon down.
Diego, wait--
Diego?!
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
If you won't listen to me,
then I'll protect you the way I know how.
Well… I'm so happy that you're on board.
And I'm thankful that,
despite your differences
with my daughter, we can still be friends.
Oh.
-Here's my card.
-Oh. Thank you.
Here's mine.
All right.
[exhales] Helena.
I didn't think I'd be
this comfortable around you.
You're like the glamorous mother
that I never had.
-So… bye.
-Bye.
Say goodbye to the world soon, Lily Cruz.
[eerie music]
Hello, Madam?
[Helena] Mercedes…
-Meet me at the VIP room.
-Right away.
[suspenseful music playing]
Madam? Who were you talking to?
Are you working for my enemy?
Are you Mercedes Palacio?
[suspenseful music continues]
Um… It's okay!
You can have this table. I'm done, anyway.
[Mercedes] Thank you.
-Miss.
-Yes?
Next time, don't mix up
the reservations, okay?
Uh, okay, ma'am. I'm really sorry.
[suspenseful music continues]
[somber piano music playing]
You're staying with me.
You're my little puppy dog!
What?
I'm not your little pet!
So, don't strangle me!
Use me all you want, but remember this…
You can't control me.
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
-The subscriber…
-Ah!
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
[grunts]
How dare you, Madrigal!
Why would you even come back to me
when I said for you to leave me alone?
I told you… to leave me alone.
And that's when you actually made a move.
[chuckles] Why?
Why would you kiss me…
and leave me hanging?
[scoffs] I hate you.
I hate you so much!
What's wrong with you, Natalie?
[chuckles] Can you still
do this? Natalie? Hello?
He is Madrigal.
[chuckles] Ew! Why are you so worked up?
Do you actually have feelings
for Madrigal?
[laughs] No…
You have feelings for Madrigal!
Ew! Ew! No.
Madrigal won't fall in love with you.
And he will never love you
the way he loves
Lily Cruz.
Get it?
[chuckles]
Or can he?
Can Madrigal fall in love with me?
Could he actually love me?
How?
Ivy Aguas? Or is it Lily Cruz?
Through Lily.
Through Lily!
[laughs]
[exhales]
[comical music]
[Arnaldo exhales] Uh--
You make it look so easy, but it's hard.
Uh… But thanks for helping me out.
I appreciate that you're checking on me.
Thank you so much.
You're really kind, Diego.
I must say, I'm a bit embarrassed because…
it's like you're
the older brother between us.
Tell me, I was the mature one
when we were kids, right?
[soft piano music playing]
Swallow it.
Stop that. You sound like a dying pig.
If Grandpa hears you crying,
he'll serve you for dinner.
-[Diego continues crying]
-You baby pig.
[Emilia] Starting tomorrow, I'm
gonna put you on a diet.
He's always full!
He only needs one tummy rub
before he falls asleep like a pig!
It's true.
Yeah.
In that case, I really need to learn this.
[ring clattering]
[bittersweet music playing]
[young Julio]
I have something else for you.
It's a promise ring. Helena, I love you.
I promise to marry you
and be with you forever.
Once I achieve my dream
of becoming president,
you'll be my first lady.
Of course, Julio. I love you.
I love you too, Helena.
[music continues]
-Julio, wait.
-You whore! You cheated on me!
Damn you, Helena.
You give women all over
the world a bad name.
No matter how you might explain it…
you still deceived me.
[dramatic music]
You're no different from Esmeralda.
You chose a worthless man over me.
Emilia's misery isn't enough
to pay for all the pain
and humiliation you gave me.
That is why I swore to myself
that I'd make you crawl in the mud
the moment you returned to Ardiente.
[dramatic music intensifies]
Damn you, Helena! I still love you.
[sniffles]
[exhales]
[breathes deeply]
Didn't you push me away the other day?
I knew it.
You like me.
No.
I would never blur the lines
between someone I'm just sleeping with.
Besides, I know exactly what
kind of relationship we have.
Then why'd you ask me to come here?
Because I want to make a proposal.
I want to help Lily.
In her fight against the Ardientes.
I've made up my mind.
Lily doesn't need your help.
Maybe.
For now.
It's gonna be a tactical alliance.
And it should've been like that
a long time ago
since we have the same enemies.
Really?
All right. Tell me.
What made you change your mind?
Well…
I've decided that I want to place my bets
and my resources on the winning team.
And I think…
Lily's in the right.
And I want to fight for what's right.
Are you sure?
Mm-hm.
[bleak string music playing]
All right. If you say so.
[Natalie chuckles]
Lily, are you sure
you saw Helena Montoya
with Mercedes Palacio?
Well, I can't be too sure.
But something tells me that Helena Montoya
is somehow connected to Mercedes Palacio.
[phone ringing]
Speak of the devil.
-Helena!
-Lily!
I called to say
how much I enjoyed our lunch.
Mmm… Me too. I feel the same way.
[Helena] So, when is our next lunch date?
That way, we can talk about our project.
[chuckles]
Well, my schedule's a little tight.
But don't worry, my
people will call your people.
I can't wait to see you again, my friend.
Bye.
[suspenseful music swelling]
Mercedes.
It's either Lily didn't see us,
or she's just pretending she
doesn't know we're connected.
Either way, we have to be careful.
She can't find out
that we know each other.
[tense music playing]
[Jenny] Here are the roses we
picked from the garden, ma'am.
All right. Wait. Is the food ready?
Yes, ma'am. The chef's preparing it.
Very good. Okay.
Well, well, well…
If there's one thing you really
got from your mother…
it's how excited you get
whenever there's a party being thrown.
You can't flatter your way
to get an invitation, Papa.
Oh, I don't need an invitation.
All I have to do is show up!
Or have you forgotten…
that this is my house?
Besides…
how can there even be a reunion
when my grandson isn't here?
Don't worry, Papa. He's on his way here.
-This flower isn't any good…
-We'll see.
Oh, no. Let's change this. Okay.
-[Julio scoffs]
-[Emilia humming]
If you need anything… just let me know.
Thanks.
[suspenseful music playing]
-What do you want?
-We're taking Arnaldo back home!
Stay out of this!
Didn't I say I wasn't going with you?
You don't have a choice anymore.
Now, come with us.
-Wait!
-Let me go! Let me go!
-[grunts] Let me go! Let me go!
-Take him!
-Diego!
-[bodyguard grunts]
[Arnaldo grunts]
[Arnaldo grunting] Let go of me!
[groans]
[grunting]
[Arnaldo groaning]
Watch out! [grunts]
[screams]
[bodyguard grunts]
[bodyguard groans]
Go on! Try me!
Leave now while you can!
-[bodyguard groans]
-Leave!
Arnaldo.
[car engine turns over]
[panting]
[tense music playing]
Are you all right?
[panting] Yes. How about you?
[panting]
Thanks.
It's about time. You're late.
I don't think you're invited
to the occasion.
[laughs] This is my house.
And whether you like it or not,
we're still family.
[scoffs]
Poor little Julio. Still hoping
we'll get back together.
-I never said that.
-You were my husband.
I know you inside and out.
I have no doubt in my heart.
I know that you still love me.
[laughs] Come on, Helena.
If I kiss you right now,
would you stop me?
[dramatic music]
[laughs] Got you!
[Helena laughing]
This is not funny.
[suspenseful music swelling]
Hello, Madam?
I'll find you, Mercedes Palacio.
And I'll know your connection
to Helena Montoya.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
but they ganged up on us.
He didn't let us take Diego Torillo.
-What do I even pay you for?!
-My goodness.
-You idiot!
-Emilia, darling.
Emilia. Come on. Calm down.
It's okay, baby. It's okay.
[Emilia sighs]
Are you okay?
It's okay. You can go, darling.
I'm sorry for wasting your time, Mama.
Oh, it's okay, my dear.
I can always meet my grandson
some other time.
But I hope nothing comes between
me and Arnaldo next time.
And you're right, Emilia.
Diego is a thorn.
So, if you don't do something
about it tonight…
then you are the biggest thorn
in this family!
[tense music playing]
Damian, is there really
no stopping you from leaving?
Damian, we're your family.
No matter what problems you have,
we can face them together.
We can trust Lily to handle herself
against Red Dragon.
And if you stay here,
you can protect Lily,
and Lily can protect you,
especially since you've already left
Red Dragon's syndicate.
Damian, don't forget we all love you.
Whatever it is you're going through,
remember that we're ready
to fight with you,
as long as you stay true to us.
[tense music playing]
[phone rings]
Hello?
Weren't you tasked to get
Diego Torillo's head?
Have you started?
Resistance is futile Jaguar.
You know that.
Or should I just kill you
together with Camia and Lily?
[tense music playing]
What are you doing here?
-[grunts]
-[Damian] Take him.
-[woman] Jaguar! Finish him!
-[gunshots]
[Diego] Dad?
[Helena] Don't worry about
the existence of Lily Cruz.
We'll take our time.
[Lily] Mercedes Palacio
and Helena Montoya.
Hello? Mercedes, can you hear me?
[Lily] I can hear you loud and clear.
You, Helena Montoya,
are none other than Red Dragon.
[theme music playing]